[
  {
    "chapter": 1,
    "title": "Introduction",
    "abstract": "abstracts/1_chapter.md"
  },
  {
    "chapter": 2,
    "title": "Miscellaneous Math",
    "abstract": "abstracts/2_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/2/2.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/2/2.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/2/2.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/2/2.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/2/2.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/2/2.3_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/2/2.4_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/2/2.4_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/2/2.5_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/2/2.5_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/2/2.6_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/2/2.6_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/2/2.7_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/2/2.7_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/2/2.8_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/2/2.8_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/2/2.9_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/2/2.9_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/2/2.10_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/2/2.10_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/2/2.11_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/2/2.11_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/2/2.12_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/2/2.12_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/2/2.13_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/2/2.13_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/2/2.14_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/2/2.14_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 3,
    "title": "Raster Images",
    "abstract": "abstracts/3_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/3/3.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/3/3.1_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 4,
    "title": "Ray Tracing",
    "abstract": "abstracts/4_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/4/4.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/4/4.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/4/4.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/4/4.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/4/4.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/4/4.3_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 5,
    "title": "Linear Algebra",
    "abstract": "abstracts/5_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/5/5.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/5/5.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/5/5.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/5/5.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/5/5.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/5/5.3_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/5/5.4_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/5/5.4_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/5/5.5_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/5/5.5_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/5/5.6_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/5/5.6_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/5/5.7_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/5/5.7_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/5/5.8_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/5/5.8_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/5/5.9_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/5/5.9_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/5/5.10_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/5/5.10_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/5/5.11_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/5/5.11_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 6,
    "title": "Transformation Matrices",
    "abstract": "abstracts/6_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/6/6.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/6/6.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/6/6.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/6/6.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/6/6.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/6/6.3_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/6/6.4_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/6/6.4_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/6/6.5_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/6/6.5_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/6/6.6_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/6/6.6_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/6/6.7_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/6/6.7_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/6/6.8_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/6/6.8_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/6/6.9_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/6/6.9_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/6/6.10_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/6/6.10_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/6/6.11_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/6/6.11_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 7,
    "title": "Viewing",
    "abstract": "abstracts/7_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/7/7.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/7/7.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/7/7.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/7/7.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/7/7.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/7/7.3_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/7/7.4_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/7/7.4_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/7/7.5_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/7/7.5_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/7/7.6_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/7/7.6_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/7/7.7_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/7/7.7_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/7/7.8_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/7/7.8_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/7/7.9_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/7/7.9_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/7/7.10_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/7/7.10_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/7/7.11_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/7/7.11_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 8,
    "title": "The Graphics Pipeline",
    "abstract": "abstracts/8_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/8/8.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/8/8.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/8/8.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/8/8.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/8/8.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/8/8.3_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/8/8.4_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/8/8.4_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/8/8.5_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/8/8.5_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 9,
    "title": "Signal Processing",
    "abstract": "abstracts/9_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/9/9.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/9/9.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/9/9.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/9/9.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/9/9.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/9/9.3_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/9/9.4_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/9/9.4_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/9/9.5_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/9/9.5_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 10,
    "title": "Surface Shading",
    "abstract": "abstracts/10_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/10/10.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/10/10.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/10/10.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/10/10.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/10/10.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/10/10.3_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 11,
    "title": "Texture Mapping",
    "abstract": "abstracts/11_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/11/11.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/11/11.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/11/11.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/11/11.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/11/11.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/11/11.3_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 12,
    "title": "Data Structures for Graphics",
    "abstract": "abstracts/12_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/12/12.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/12/12.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/12/12.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/12/12.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/12/12.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/12/12.3_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/12/12.4_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/12/12.4_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 13,
    "title": "More Ray Tracing",
    "abstract": "abstracts/13_chapter.md"
  },
  {
    "chapter": 14,
    "title": "Sampling",
    "abstract": "abstracts/14_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/14/14.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/14/14.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/14/14.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/14/14.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/14/14.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/14/14.3_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/14/14.4_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/14/14.4_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/14/14.5_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/14/14.5_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/14/14.6_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/14/14.6_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 15,
    "title": "Curves",
    "abstract": "abstracts/15_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/15/15.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/15/15.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/15/15.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/15/15.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/15/15.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/15/15.3_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/15/15.4_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/15/15.4_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/15/15.5_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/15/15.5_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/15/15.6_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/15/15.6_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/15/15.7_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/15/15.7_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/15/15.8_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/15/15.8_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/15/15.9_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/15/15.9_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 16,
    "title": "Implicit Modeling",
    "abstract": "abstracts/16_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/16/16.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/16/16.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/16/16.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/16/16.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/16/16.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/16/16.3_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/16/16.4_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/16/16.4_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 17,
    "title": "Computer Animation",
    "abstract": "abstracts/17_chapter.md"
  },
  {
    "chapter": 18,
    "title": "Using Graphics Hardware",
    "abstract": "abstracts/18_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/18/18.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/18/18.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/18/18.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/18/18.2_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 19,
    "title": "Building Interactive Graphics Applications",
    "abstract": "abstracts/19_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/19/19.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/19/19.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/19/19.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/19/19.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/19/19.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/19/19.3_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/19/19.4_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/19/19.4_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/19/19.5_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/19/19.5_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/19/19.6_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/19/19.6_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/19/19.7_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/19/19.7_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 20,
    "title": "Light",
    "abstract": "abstracts/20_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/20/20.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/20/20.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/20/20.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/20/20.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/20/20.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/20/20.3_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 21,
    "title": "Color",
    "abstract": "abstracts/21_chapter.md"
  },
  {
    "chapter": 22,
    "title": "Visual Perception",
    "abstract": "abstracts/22_chapter.md"
  },
  {
    "chapter": 23,
    "title": "Tone Reproduction",
    "abstract": "abstracts/23_chapter.md"
  },
  {
    "chapter": 24,
    "title": "Global Illumination",
    "abstract": "abstracts/24_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/24/24.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/24/24.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/24/24.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/24/24.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/24/24.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/24/24.3_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/24/24.4_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/24/24.4_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/24/24.5_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/24/24.5_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/24/24.6_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/24/24.6_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 25,
    "title": "Reflection Models",
    "abstract": "abstracts/25_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/25/25.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/25/25.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/25/25.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/25/25.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/25/25.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/25/25.3_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 26,
    "title": "Computer Graphics in Games",
    "abstract": "abstracts/26_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/26/26.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/26/26.1_response.md"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "chapter": 27,
    "title": "Visualization",
    "abstract": "abstracts/27_chapter.md"
  },
  {
    "chapter": 28,
    "title": "Spatial-Field Visualization",
    "abstract": "abstracts/28_chapter.md",
    "exercises": [
      {
        "question": "exercises/28/28.1_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/28/28.1_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/28/28.2_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/28/28.2_response.md"
      },
      {
        "question": "exercises/28/28.3_question.md",
        "response": "exercises/28/28.3_response.md"
      }
    ]
  }
]
